[{"answer": "Romulan ale should be illegal", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Then it should be more illegal", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": " Now, you make a toast", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "New worlds.  Yes Data, brave new worlds..", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Do you know who I am", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "No.  My name is Data... I am your brother", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": " We're sending you all the intelligence we have, but it's not much.  I don't need to tell you to watch your back, my friend", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "  The Son'a, the Borg, the that place, the evil my friend and that pesky Nexus.  You seem to get all the easy assignments", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Come to dinner on my friend tomorrow. Just the two of us.  Or just the one of us", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "I know", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "When was he... created", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": " I think a skin cell's the more likely of the two", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "He can never know you as I know you... He can never touch you as I touch you", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Can you feel my hands... are they real?  Can you feel my lips, my loins", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "I have no reason to", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "And if you had lived my life you would understand that there is a great responsibility in representing the Federation.  I can't let my personal feelings unduly influence my decisions", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Maybe I'll train it to do little tricks for me like your robot does. Or maybe I'll snap its ugly head off", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "It's about destiny, my friend.  About a Reman outcast wh", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "And I'm not quite human.  So what am I?  What do you see?  Do you see a life you might have led?  Lost youth never to be recaptured", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I see an old man, set in his ways, afraid to live without a uniform to prop him up and a Starfleet regulation to tell him what to do. I see the man I will never be", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "I know you as well as I know myself, that place.  There was a time you looked at the stars and dreamed of what might be", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Not so long", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Not so long", "docId": "startrek10.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I see more than what you are", "qsentId": 24}]